<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Flint</string>
    <string name="details_activity">Details</string>

    <!-- Image descriptions -->
    <string name="image_description">Flint image</string>
    <string name="image_background_description">Background for opaque image</string>

    <!-- Attractions Fragment -->
    <string name="crossraods_village_name">Crossroads Village and Huckleberry Railroad</string>
    <string name="crossraods_village_distance">Tourist attraction in Genesee, Michigan</string>
    <string name="crossraods_village_details">1800s-era lakeside village offers 34 historic buildings
        and a working train plus family activities.</string>
    <string name="crossraods_village_description">What was yesterday really like? How simple was that
        simpler time? There’s a place where history comes to life and you’re part of the experience.
        It’s Crossroads Village, our one-of-a-kind collection of restored 19th century buildings,
        amusement rides and authentic narrow-gauge railroad. Here you’ll see what life “way back
        when” was all about. From the smithing of the iron to the churning of the butter to the
        pressing of the cider. And so much more. </string>
    <string name="crossraods_village_location">6140 N Bray Rd, Flint, MI 48505</string>

    <string name="sloan_museum_name">Sloan Museum</string>
    <string name="sloan_museum_distance">Museum in Burton, Michigan</string>
    <string name="sloan_museum_detail">Specializes in the local history of Genesee County and the Flint area,
        particularly in connection with the rise and decline of the local auto industry.</string>
    <string name="sloan_museum_description">The Sloan Museum is a public museum located within the
        Flint Cultural Center in Flint, Michigan. The museum specializes in the local history of
        Genesee County and the Flint area, particularly in connection with the rise and decline of
        the local auto industry. The museum, named in honor of longtime General Motors chief
        executive officer Alfred P. Sloan, operates a cycle of special exhibitions and
        celebrations.</string>
    <string name="sloan_museum_location">4190 E Court St, Burton, MI 48509</string>

    <string name="institute_of_arts_name">Flint Institute of Arts</string>
    <string name="institute_of_arts_distance">Museum in Flint, Michigan</string>
    <string name="institute_of_arts_detail">The second largest art museum in Michigan</string>
    <string name="institute_of_arts_description">The Flint Institute of Arts is the second largest
        art museum in the State of Michigan and one of the largest museum art schools in the nation.
        Each year, more than 160,000 people visit the FIA’s galleries and participate in FIA programs
        and services.</string>
    <string name="institute_of_arts_location">1120 E Kearsley St, Flint, MI 48503</string>

    <string name="planetarium_name">Longway Planetarium</string>
    <string name="planetarium_distance">Planetarium in Flint, Michigan</string>
    <string name="planetarium_detail">Astronomy demonstrations, classes and camps plus science and
        laser rock shows under a 60-ft. dome.</string>
    <string name="planetarium_description">Longway Planetarium presents educational and entertaining
        shows exploring astronomy and science topics every day of the week!</string>
    <string name="planetarium_location">1310 E. Kearsley St. Flint, MI 48503</string>


    <!-- Colleges Fragment -->
    <string name="kettering_name">Kettering University</string>
    <string name="kettering_distance">Private university in Flint, Michigan</string>
    <string name="kettering_detail">Kettering University is a private cooperative education and
        experiential learning-based university in Flint, Michigan, offering bachelor\'s and master\'s
        degrees in STEM and business fields. </string>
    <string name="kettering_description">Kettering University (formerly General Motors Institute of
        Technology) is a private cooperative education and experiential learning based university in
        Flint, Michigan, offering bachelor\'s and master\'s degrees in STEM (Science, Technology,
        Engineering, and Mathematics) and business fields. Students participate in a co-op based
        education with a unique schedule featuring 6 months of a full time job at a participating
        company (such as Ford Motor Company, General Motors, and many more).</string>
    <string name="kettering_location">1700 University Ave, Flint, MI 48504</string>

    <string name="um_flint_name">University of Michigan-Flint</string>
    <string name="um_flint_distance">Public university in Flint, Michigan</string>
    <string name="um_flint_detail">One of the two University of Michigan satellite campuses.</string>
    <string name="um_flint_description">The University of Michigan–Flint is rated as one of the best
        master\'s-level public universities in the Midwest by US News and World Report. The Princeton
        Review has included UM–Flint in the "Best in the Midwest" category in their publication 2014
        Best Colleges: Region by Region. The Part-Time MBA Program is ranked 41st in the United
        States (overall) and 9th in the Midwest (by region).</string>
    <string name="um_flint_location">303 E Kearsley St, Flint, MI 48502</string>

    <string name="mott_cc_name">Mott Community College</string>
    <string name="mott_cc_distance">Community college in Flint, Michigan</string>
    <string name="mott_cc_detail">The college offers 61 associate degrees and 40 pre-associate certificates.</string>
    <string name="mott_cc_description">It has satellite campuses in nearby Clio, Fenton,
        Lapeer, and Howell. With over 10,00 students, Mott CC offers associates degrees with the
        majority of students continuing education afterwards.</string>
    <string name="mott_cc_location">1401 E Court St, Flint, MI 48503</string>

    <!-- Food Fragment -->
    <string name="churchills_name">Churchill\'s Food and Spirits</string>
    <string name="churchills_distance">Downtown Flint</string>
    <string name="churchills_detail">Draft brews, bar food and live music in an old-school atmosphere
        with brick walls and an outdoor patio.</string>
    <string name="churchills_description">Churchill’s Food and Spirits was established in 1980 and has
        remained a staple of downtown Flint. It is our mission to provide the highest quality of
        service possible using the highest quality of locally sourced ingredients spirits and brews
        we can get our hands on. We take pride in being recognized as the premiere whiskey bar and
        restaurant in the Flint area, while ranking among the best in the state of Michigan.</string>
    <string name="churchills_location">340 Saginaw St, Flint, MI 48502</string>

    <string name="crepe_company_name">Flint Crepe Company</string>
    <string name="crepe_company_distance">Crêperie in Downtown Flint</string>
    <string name="crepe_company_detail">Airy spot with industrial ceiling dispensing creative sweet
        and savory crepes from local ingredients.</string>
    <string name="crepe_company_description">Flint-roasted coffee and locally sourced ingredients,
        savory and sweet crepes, homemade food. Ranked as one of Michigan’s Top 10 coffee shops with
        a chai latte renowned state-wide, the Flint Crepe Co. also is home to unique and delicious
        farm-to-fork meals.</string>
    <string name="crepe_company_location">555 Saginaw St, Flint, MI 48502</string>

    <string name="white_horse_name">White Horse Tavern</string>
    <string name="white_horse_distance">Downtown Flint</string>
    <string name="white_horse_detail">Circa-1973 family-run pub serving breakfast, American faves
        and 10 beers on tap, open until 2 AM.</string>
    <string name="white_horse_description">At the White Horse Tavern, we\'ve been cooking up great
        burgers, pizzas, and more for the hardworking people of Flint, MI for 40 years!</string>
    <string name="white_horse_location">621 W Court St, Flint, MI 48503</string>

    <!-- Events Fragment -->
    <string name="market_name">Flint Farmers Market</string>
    <string name="market_distance">Downtown Flint</string>
    <string name="market_detail">Open all year, come one come all spring winter and fall. Enjoy great food,
        entertainment, kitchen demonstrations, events and more.</string>
    <string name="market_description">We’re a year round public market with 50+ vendors inside the
        building and more outside. Our market is neat and clean and feature several produce vendors,
        a great meat market, poultry, breads and baked goods, cheese, a wine shop, an art gallery,
        a cafe, middle-eastern and Mexican groceries, and many unique gifts. </string>
    <string name="market_location">300 E 1st St, Flint, MI 48502</string>

    <string name="crim_name">Flint Crim 5k</string>
    <string name="crim_distance">Across Flint</string>
    <string name="crim_detail">Yearly marathon with training and classes offered throughout the year</string>
    <string name="crim_description">The Crim Festival of Races is an annual road running event with
        several races and walking events. The original distance was 10 miles (16 kilometers) and is
        the marque race as "The Crim" with its infamous Bradley Hills and blue line to keep runners
        on course. The Crim has been held in August in Flint, Michigan since 1977. It draws runners
        from around the world from countries such as Kenya, Russia, and Ukraine. The race attracts
        approximately 50,000 people each year.</string>
    <string name="crim_location">452 Saginaw St, Flint, MI 48502</string>

    <string name="back_to_bricks_name">Back to the Bricks</string>
    <string name="back_to_bricks_distance">Downtown Flint</string>
    <string name="back_to_bricks_detail">Famous car show with thousands of visitors and participants</string>
    <string name="back_to_bricks_description">The five-day extravaganza begins on Tuesday with
        "Bricks Flicks," a family-oriented party at the nostalgic US-23 Drive-In theatre on Fenton
        Road. During the main event week, excited crowds line the streets for the “Rolling Cruises”
        as the parade route stretches from the "red bricks" of Saginaw Street in downtown Flint to
        the city of Grand Blanc. On Friday, there will be a car show, concert, and dance party with
        a Motown theme.  Thousands will stroll the brick streets on Saturday to admire vehicles of
        every age and description, take pictures, buy souvenirs, and enjoy the fun. Beginning with
        the Opening Ceremony, you will want to be there to experience the excitement, see the
        amazing car show, check out the automotive vendors, and taste the delicious food that is
        synonymous with Back to the Bricks®, one of the best Classic Car Events in the Nation.</string>
    <string name="back_to_bricks_location">6452 Marble Ln, Flushing, MI 48433</string>

</resources>
